https://meditationinexeter.org/privacy-policy/

next eventHomeAbout usWho we areRooms for rentGet involvedKadampa BuddhismTeachersPrivacy PolicyMeditation classesWhat to expectMonday eveningsTuesday morningsTuesday eveningExeter RD&E Wednesday lunchtimesThursday morningsThursday eveningsExeter In-depth studyEventsContact infoCovid-19 precautionsViewing a live-stream
HomeAbout usWho we areRooms for rentGet involvedKadampa BuddhismTeachersPrivacy PolicyMeditation classesWhat to expectMonday eveningsTuesday morningsTuesday eveningExeter RD&E Wednesday lunchtimesThursday morningsThursday eveningsExeter In-depth studyEventsContact infoCovid-19 precautionsViewing a live-streamFrom Thursday 5th November all our classes will be online only until further notice.
Home
About usWho we areRooms for rentGet involvedKadampa BuddhismTeachersPrivacy Policy
Meditation classesWhat to expectMonday eveningsTuesday morningsTuesday eveningExeter RD&E Wednesday lunchtimesThursday morningsThursday eveningsExeter In-depth study Events Contact infoCovid-19 precautions
Viewing a live-stream
Home
About usWho we areRooms for rentGet involvedKadampa BuddhismTeachersPrivacy Policy
Meditation classesWhat to expectMonday eveningsTuesday morningsTuesday eveningExeter RD&E Wednesday lunchtimesThursday morningsThursday eveningsExeter In-depth study Events Contact infoCovid-19 precautions
Viewing a live-stream
01392 490058Pure Land Kadampa Buddhist Centre Privacy Policy Notice This is the privacy notice of Pure Land Kadampa Buddhist Centre (referred to as “we”, “our”, “us” or “Pure Land” in this document). We are a Registered Charity, number 1052954 and Company, number 3097070. Introduction This notice sets out the basis on which we collect personal data that could be used to identify you and how we collect, store and process that data. It also explains your rights and options regarding the ways in which your personal information is used and collected, and our obligations to you. We are committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal information at all times. Our policy complies with UK law accordingly implemented, including that required by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Information we collect from you We only collect personal information that you have provided direct to us, for example when requesting information, booking an event or subscribing to the mailing list. We do not obtain information from third parties. The personal information we collect will vary depending on the circumstance and may include your full name and title, postal address, e-mail address, and phone number(s). The data that you provide to us is collected by email, by post, in person, by telephone, or the website mailing list or booking facility. How we use your information The information we collect is used to manage your bookings and to contact you about any issues relating to your booking, for example to confirm or cancel a booking. We will only contact you if we are responding to a request from you or we have your permission to do so. Data for memberships and enrolled study programmes is collected for the purposes of administering your membership and enrolment and in maintaining contact with you during your membership and/or studies. It may for example, be used to send you email updates about your study programme, personal communications relevant to your study or membership from Centre staff/managers and other pertinent information about the Centre and its activities. We do not normally share or disclose information to third parties. However, in exceptional circumstances, where there is a significant risk to your health and wellbeing or the health and wellbeing of another person or to comply with the law, we may need to disclose information to a third party, for example, medical profession or a law enforcement agency. If this is likely to be necessary, we will discuss this with you wherever possible. We will never sell or rent your information to third parties and will never share your Information with third parties for marketing purposes. How long we keep your personal information? Your information will be retained for a period of 6 years plus the current year, for statutory record keeping purposes. After this time, unless we have a legal obligation to retain it for longer, your personal information will be deleted or, where data is required for statistical purposes, anonymised. Your information used for marketing purposes will be kept until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. Access to and amending your personal information You may contact us at any time to request a copy, amend, or remove your personal information or restrict the way in which we use it. If you wish to be removed from our mailing list please click the “unsubscribe” link on any of our events emails. If you contact us by email or post we will only edit or delete your information when we have successfully confirmed your identify. How your information is managed and stored We take appropriate and proportionate measures to ensure that the personal information we collect remains safe and secure. All confidential paperwork is securely destroyed. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We will use strict procedures and security features to strive to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. Protection of Children We only process personal information relating to children under the age of 16 with consent from whoever holds parental responsibility. Children over the age of 16 may join the mailing list themselves or provide us with their personal information when attending an event. If we are concerned about the maturity of a child to give consent we will seek consent from the person with parental responsibility. Information collected will be processed in accordance with this Privacy Notice. Children have the same rights as adults with respect to this Privacy Notice. Third Party Links Our website and our email communications may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have no control. Any information you provide to third party websites will be governed under the terms of each websites’ privacy policy and we encourage you to check their policies before disclosing any information. We have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content, actions or policies of third party websites. The inclusion of third party websites on our site does not constitutes an endorsement of such websites’ content, actions or policies. We use a third party provider, Paypal, to process payment information. For more information please see PayPal’s’ Privacy Policy. We use third party providers, Vertical Response and Mailchimp, to deliver mailing list emails. For more information please see their privacy policy. If you use the Eventbrite booking service, your personal contact information is stored within the Eventbrite database and we encourage you to check their privacy policy. Photographs We occasionally take photographs at classes and events for use in our publicity materials, website, and social media. If you do not wish to have an image of you used for such purposes, please contact us as detailed below, or advise a teacher, volunteer or the photographer at the time. Should you find an image of yourself on any of our materials or on-line sites and wish for it to be removed, please also contact us as detailed below. Website Statistics We may also collect information about how our website is accessed and used (“Usage Data”) to improve the performance of the website. This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our website and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyse our website. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website. Examples of Cookies we use: Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our website.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings. Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes Changes to this privacy notice We may update this privacy notice from time to time to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other legal or regulatory reasons.
This privacy notice was last updated on 29th January 2018. Complaints If you are in any way dissatisfied about how we process your personal information, please contact us as detailed below. You may also lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/ How to Contact Us You can contact us either by email or post: Email:admin@meditationinexeter.orgPostal address: Pure Land Kadampa Buddhist Centre, 55 Union Road, Exeter, Devon, EX4 6HU Published: 29th January 2018
We use cookies to allow us to better understand how the site is used. By continuing to use this site, you consent to this policy. Click to learn moreAgree & Continue
Translate »
